

N ATALIJA N IKOLIĆ

3 D ARTIST

Professional 3D Artist with over 3 years of experience in the VFX industry, dedicated to producing compelling visuals for film, television, and commercials. Bringing a fresh perspective to projects, combining technical expertise with a passion for storytelling to create immersive visual experiences

CONTACT

Email:

nikolic.natalija7@gmail.com

Website:

https://natalija-nikolic98.github.io/

SKILLS

- Creative
- Innovative
- Team player
- Communicative
- Adaptive
- Detail-oriented
- Research

SOFTWARE

- Unreal Engine
- Autodesk Maya
- ZBrush
- Pftrack
- Adobe Substance Painter
- DaVinci

EDUCATION

THE COLLEGE OF FINE AND APPLIED ARTS

2017 - 2020

Bachelor's Degree - Image Media

2020 - 2023

Master's Degree - Audio Visual Composition

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE - DIGITAL ARTIST

2019 - 2021

- Illustrations
- Video Editing

QLBEANS - 3D AND MATCHMOVE ARTIST

2021 - Present

- Matchmove
- 3D Modeling

CERTIFICATION

Unreal Fellowship: Storytelling

2023